fetise.com 2013-05-03

# Privacy Policy : Fetise.com, India's leading fashion and lifestyle online store

You Can Count On Us

Your privacy is important to us at Fetise.com. That's why we've outlined the types of personal information that we receive and collect when you use our site; and the steps we take to safeguard your personal information. We hope this will help you to make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

Fetise.com strives to maintain the highest standards of integrity and discretion in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting the privacy of both our registered users and site visitors. 

Use of Personal Information

Fetise.com collects personally identifiable information from visitors to our website on a voluntary basis. This information is limited to first name, last name, gender, email address, date of birth, postal address and telephone number. A subset of this personal information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us.

We require these details only to provide you the services we offer. We use your address to deliver the order and use your mobile number and e-mail address to send you order and shipping confirmations. Additionally if you opt in for e-mail and SMS product updates we send these notifications on the mobile number and/or email ID provided. Your personal information is shared on a need to know basis with specific trusted employees who are involved in servicing your order. Please note that any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary and potentially legal action. 

Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies to enable you to personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. 

The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the site pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables Fetise.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. 

We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. However, no personally identifiable information you give us is divulged for cookie or web beacon use, meaning YOU cannot be identified by our partners.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies or get a notification when a cookie is being sent by modifying your Web browser. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may have a depleted experience of our website. Privacy software may also be used to override web beacons; this should not cause a problem with using our site. 

Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement across the site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used for internal operations and is and not shared with any third-party.

Updates and Effective Date

Fetise.com reserves the right to make changes to our privacy policy. If there is a material change in our practices, we will indicate such changes on this page and inform our registered users on the site homepage and/or via e-mail. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to our privacy policy as stated above, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site. 

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
